ragezone.com 2019-12-15

# RaGEZONE Privacy Policy

                                     RaGEZONE Privacy Policy
This policy covers all domains related to ragezone.com including sub-domains.
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use
personal information collected at this site and legislation to company representatives.
Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal
information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this
privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted
and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not
retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit
the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide
will be used.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email
addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you
provide is used to fulfil you specific request. This information is only used to fulfil
your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for
example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered.
Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as
browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and
understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site
for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking
technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information,
cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information
may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting
us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or
required by law; or, trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or
unauthorized transactions; or, investigating fraud which has already taken place. The
information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees,
agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential)
have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to
opt out of further mailings.
Legal departments and development
Under no circumstances can RaGEZONE be held responsible for data posted or

provided by us or members. All files are subject to public data and are obtained
legally and are distributed legally via the freedom of information act. If you are in any
relation to any company which software appears on this web site you have no right
under any circumstances to view any of the content. By viewing any of the content
provided by RaGEZONE you are breaking our terms of service. We are not legally
responsible for how the information is presented, shared or distributed via our servers
(including third party). If you do wish to forward a DMCA complaint regardless of
our terms please visit the bottom of this document.
Emulated and replicated servers
All servers provided by us are at no charge at all, all servers are provided and run for
the intentions of fun and personal achievement, and under no circumstances are we
personally responsible for the loss of members to any game which we provide (legal
or replicated). RaGEZONE and staff whom provide and run these servers cannot be
held legally responsible for any financial loss and if you are in any relation to any
company that provides these servers you have no permission to access or contact our
service provider. This also goes for any server advertisements posted on our forums,
we take no responsibility for a third party's actions.
Personal liability
Any person(s) whom use our services which neglect time for themselves including,
work, children or any personal or life related issue cannot hold RaGEZONE
responsible, in the event that service members have destroyed your life , they are
not legally accountable, any person who chooses to use such resources for extensive
periods of time only have themselves to blame. In the event of suicide, all media
publicity shall be used to the maximum, but any legal proceedings shall be ignored
due to the possible mentality of that person.
Subscription and advertising service
Any person(s) who subscribe or purchase advertising to a RaGEZONE service shall not
receive a refund once the subscription or advertising has gone live. Our subscription system is
automated thus no refunds are given unless there is a system error.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may
contact us using the information below:
DMCA Notice; (Server is physically located in Russia as of 2011)
RaGEZONE.com is in compliance with 17 U.S.C. & 512 and the Digital Millennium
Copyright Act ("DMCA"). It is our policy to respond to any infringement notices and
take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") and

other applicable intellectual property laws.
If you find any material that has been indexed by this website that is not compliant
with our Terms of Service and wish to send an abuse report or to request for any
objectionable content to be removed, please provide the following documentation:
1. The words "DMCA COMPLAINT" at the top of your communication.
2. A description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property you claim has
been infringed.
3. Evidence that you own the copyright to, or evidence that you are a representative
of, the entity owning the infringed work or intellectual property.
4. The date you originally published or registered this work.
5. The date you discovered the infringement.
6. The URL(s) furnishing unlicensed copies of your work.
7. The action you believe RaGEZONE.com should take to correct the problem.
8. The following statement or equivalent: "I have a good faith belief that use of the
copyrighted materials described above on the allegedly infringing web pages is not
authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law. I swear, under penalty of
perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate and that I am the copyright
owner or am authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is
allegedly infringed."
9. Your company name (if any), your legal name (printed), your mailing address,
and your phone number.
10. Your signature (or digital signature), and the present date.
11. You complaint MUST include all of the above information.
Note carefully that you will be liable for damages, costs, and attorneys' fees if you
misrepresent that a product or activity is infringing your copyrights. Prior to filing a
DMCA complaint we suggest that you first contact an attorney.
Details of the DMCA are available at US Copyright Office Web Site:
www.copyright.gov.

Physical Contact Address
RaGEZONE
Mailbox 451
Apex House
Thomas Street
Trethomas
Caerphilly
CF83 8DP
Contact Email Address
admin at ragezone dot com
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be
posted.
Last updated: 15/11/2012
